cricketarchive.com 2019-03-20

# Privacy Policy - CricketArchive

CricketArchive Limited knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy describes our privacy policy with respect to the information collected on this Site. By visiting cricketarchive.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Names of data controller**   
CricketArchive Limited (Cricket Archive)

**Contact details:**

CricketArchive Ltd  
49 Heworth Village  
York  
YO31 1AE  
Email: email@cricketarchive.com  
Phone: 0203 1981 359

**Categories of personal data**   
Full name  
Email address  
Billing address (optional)  
Payment information

**What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Collect It?**  
The information we gather on this Site falls into two categories: (1) personal information you supply, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our Site.

**Personally Identifiable Information  
** We will collect personally identifiable information whenever you register your account at the Site, or update your registration information. To apply for a log-in account to access the Site, we ask you to provide personally identifiable information, including but not limited to, your name, address, phone number, and email address.

Please note you also may be asked to provide credit card information to the extent you are paying the online subscription fee. Credit card information is processed by CricketArchive Limited's third party vendors. CricketArchive Limited itself does not collect or store any User's credit card information, and CricketArchive Limited is not responsible for maintaining the security or privacy of any information that you provide, including credit card information, in connection with purchasing products or services via the Site.

**Purposes of processing**   
Cricket Archive will process your personal data for the purposes of:

  * Servicing your subscription
  * Identification purposes
  * Quality and improvement monitoring
  * Direct marketing if you have consented to this
  * Profiling for marketing and insight purposes

**How will you use my email address?**   
We will use your email to update you about your subscription to Cricket Archive. We will not send you any marketing material unless you have consented us to do so. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us at [email@cricketarchive.com](mailto:email@cricketarchive.com). 

**Aggregate Information**  
When you use this Site, we may collect tracking information such as your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and the pages you visited on the Site. None of this information identifies you personally; we collect it for aggregate reporting on site activity. For example, we may want to know how long the average user spends on this Site, or which pages or features get the most attention. We use this information to make the Site more useful.

**Web Beacons**  
We may use "Web Beacon" (also known as "clear GIF", "pixel tag", "data tag" or "image tag") technology to collect anonymous, non-personal information about how this Site is used. We will use this information to make improvements to this Site and to help us plan for technical improvements. This information will not identify you or any other user of this Site as an individual.

 **E-Mail**  
We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails that tell us whether or not you can accept HTML images and, if you can accept HTML, whether or not you viewed the e-mail. We use this information to help us make our e-mails more useful and interesting. This process does not leave any information on your computer, nor does it collect information from your computer. We do not share or sell this information to others, and we only use it to improve our e-mail communications with you.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a block of text placed in a file on your hard drive by a website you've visited. We use cookies to understand how visitors to this Site click to it and what pages they view during their visit. We do not store any personal information in any cookie at any time.

We may also use third party service providers for research purposes, including helping us to measure and analyse how visitors click to and use the Site. To do this, we may use cookies or web beacons provided by these third parties to track the types of non-personal information described above. Such aggregated information is used within CricketArchive Limited's internal organisation and is only shared with third parties on an aggregated and non-personally identifiable basis.

The "help" function on most browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don't accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of various features on this Site that are available to other visitors.

**Legal basis for processing your personal data:**

The legal basis for the collection and processing of your personal data is:

  * Administration and identification: that it is necessary to fulfil the contract that you are going to enter into or have entered into with us
  * Direct marketing – which may include profiling for the purposes of direct marketing that you have given your consent
  * In all other cases: that it is necessary for our legitimate interests and does not prejudice or harm your rights and freedoms

**Does CricketArchive Limited Share the Information It Receives?**  
Although information about those who visit our web site is important to us, we are not in the business of selling that information to others.

We may provide aggregate information that does not identify particular individuals, such as the number or percentage of visitors who fall within certain category or categories, to a third party.  
We may also share your information with third parties in the following circumstances:

• Service Providers: We employ third party service providers to perform functions on our behalf, including, for example, the processing of online subscriptions. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending mail, analysing data, providing marketing assistance, and processing credit card payments.

• Legal Obligations: From time to time, we may be required to share personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful.

• Protection of CricketArchive Limited and Others: We will release the names of account holders and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply the Terms of Use for this Site and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of cricketarchive.com, our users, or others. However, this does not include selling, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Your right to withdraw consent  
**You have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. If you do, it will not affect the lawfulness of any processing for which we had consent prior to your withdrawing it.

**How Secure is the Information that CricketArchive Limited Collects?**  
We strive to keep information such as your name and email address safe, and employ stringent security measures to make sure that your information is not unintentionally shared with others. Despite our efforts, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Third party links  
** The site may also contain links to third party sites that are not under our control. These sites have their own policies regarding privacy, and you should review these policies before providing information to these sites. CricketArchive Limited has no responsibility for linked websites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. CricketArchive Limited also maintains a strict "no-spam" policy.

**Location of your personal data**   
We will normally keep your personal data within the European Economic Area. Data is normally stored in the EU but may, on occasion, be accessed for problem determination purposes by our service provider outside the EU but the access is subject to safeguards approved by law.

**How long we will keep your personal data for  
**Your personal data will be retained by Cricket Archive for 2 years following your last interaction with us.

**Your rights in respect of your personal data  
**You have the right of access to your personal data and, in some cases, to require us to restrict, erase or rectify it or to object to our processing it, and the right of data portability.

**Complaints  
**If you have any concerns or complaints about how we are handling your data please do not hesitate to get in touch by emailing us at magazine@thecricketer.com or by calling 0203 1981 359

**Terms of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit cricketarchive.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, application of the law of the United Kingdom and resolution of any disputes in the United Kingdom. If you have any concern about privacy at cricketarchive.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our website is updated frequently, and the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use for this Site may change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check this Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have collected from you through this Site. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of information collected in the past without notifying affected members, either by communicating directly with them or by posting the changes on this Site.

**Privacy Support**   
If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: [email@cricketarchive.com](mailto:email@cricketarchive.com)  

Updated 24/5/18
